{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812061071","data":{"timestamp":" 946812061070"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 647d14d0-2e33-40e6-8cfe-c8d72e6fae04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" amelala"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMELALA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812062109","data":{"timestamp":" 946812062109"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 647d14d0-2e33-40e6-8cfe-c8d72e6fae04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" amelala"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMELALA"," userResponse":" AMELALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812094895","data":{"timestamp":" 946812094895"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 647d14d0-2e33-40e6-8cfe-c8d72e6fae04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sherehe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHEREHE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812095952","data":{"timestamp":" 946812095952"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 647d14d0-2e33-40e6-8cfe-c8d72e6fae04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sherehe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHEREHE"," userResponse":" SHEREHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812113937","data":{"timestamp":" 946812113937"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 647d14d0-2e33-40e6-8cfe-c8d72e6fae04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kungoja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812115032","data":{"timestamp":" 946812115032"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 647d14d0-2e33-40e6-8cfe-c8d72e6fae04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kungoja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGOJA"," userResponse":" KUNGOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812123455","data":{"timestamp":" 946812123455"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 647d14d0-2e33-40e6-8cfe-c8d72e6fae04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" makubwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812124523","data":{"timestamp":" 946812124523"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 647d14d0-2e33-40e6-8cfe-c8d72e6fae04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" makubwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKUBWA"," userResponse":" MAKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812173118","data":{"timestamp":" 946812173118"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 647d14d0-2e33-40e6-8cfe-c8d72e6fae04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" umeiona"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMEIONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812174172","data":{"timestamp":" 946812174172"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 647d14d0-2e33-40e6-8cfe-c8d72e6fae04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" umeiona"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMEIONA"," userResponse":" UMEIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812176026","data":{"timestamp":" 946812176026"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 647d14d0-2e33-40e6-8cfe-c8d72e6fae04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" umeiona"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812176178","data":{"timestamp":" 946812176178"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 647d14d0-2e33-40e6-8cfe-c8d72e6fae04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" umeiona"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMEIONA"," userResponse":" UMEIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812185671","data":{"timestamp":" 946812185669"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 3ee5d0ea-2949-4101-8a88-8d34fee93814"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812185898","data":{"timestamp":" 946812185897"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 3ee5d0ea-2949-4101-8a88-8d34fee93814"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812186861","data":{"timestamp":" 946812186860"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 3ee5d0ea-2949-4101-8a88-8d34fee93814"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812187274","data":{"timestamp":" 946812187273"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 3ee5d0ea-2949-4101-8a88-8d34fee93814"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812187356","data":{"timestamp":" 946812187356"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 3ee5d0ea-2949-4101-8a88-8d34fee93814"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812199856","data":{"timestamp":" 946812199856"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812201951","data":{"timestamp":" 946812201951"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812204475","data":{"timestamp":" 946812204474"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812206848","data":{"timestamp":" 946812206848"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812210055","data":{"timestamp":" 946812210055"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATATIZO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812212141","data":{"timestamp":" 946812212140"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812214075","data":{"timestamp":" 946812214075"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812214682","data":{"timestamp":" 946812214682"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" CHANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812215415","data":{"timestamp":" 946812215414"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKUWA"," userResponse":" KILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812215595","data":{"timestamp":" 946812215595"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812216391","data":{"timestamp":" 946812216390"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATATIZO"," userResponse":" MATATIZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812217424","data":{"timestamp":" 946812217424"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" MENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812221151","data":{"timestamp":" 946812221151"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIPANGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812223188","data":{"timestamp":" 946812223188"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FOLENI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812228118","data":{"timestamp":" 946812228118"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEFU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812230829","data":{"timestamp":" 946812230829"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKISUBIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812233557","data":{"timestamp":" 946812233557"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHOTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812236238","data":{"timestamp":" 946812236238"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812238808","data":{"timestamp":" 946812238808"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812241692","data":{"timestamp":" 946812241692"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFEREJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812244451","data":{"timestamp":" 946812244451"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812246601","data":{"timestamp":" 946812246601"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIPANGA"," userResponse":" TULIPANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812247285","data":{"timestamp":" 946812247285"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FOLENI"," userResponse":" FOLENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812248540","data":{"timestamp":" 946812248540"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEFU"," userResponse":" NDEFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812250203","data":{"timestamp":" 946812250203"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKISUBIRI"," userResponse":" TUKISUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812250927","data":{"timestamp":" 946812250927"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHOTA"," userResponse":" KUCHOTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812251770","data":{"timestamp":" 946812251770"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812252635","data":{"timestamp":" 946812252634"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812253359","data":{"timestamp":" 946812253359"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFEREJI"," userResponse":" MFEREJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812254023","data":{"timestamp":" 946812254022"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812258074","data":{"timestamp":" 946812258073"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULISUBIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812259972","data":{"timestamp":" 946812259972"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812262186","data":{"timestamp":" 946812262186"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812264207","data":{"timestamp":" 946812264206"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812266609","data":{"timestamp":" 946812266609"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812270162","data":{"timestamp":" 946812270161"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPOKEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812273111","data":{"timestamp":" 946812273111"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAADA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812275782","data":{"timestamp":" 946812275781"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812279790","data":{"timestamp":" 946812279790"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812282103","data":{"timestamp":" 946812282103"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULISUBIRI"," userResponse":" TULISUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812282644","data":{"timestamp":" 946812282643"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812282794","data":{"timestamp":" 946812282794"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812283195","data":{"timestamp":" 946812283195"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812284032","data":{"timestamp":" 946812284031"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812284958","data":{"timestamp":" 946812284957"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPOKEA"," userResponse":" KUPOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812285660","data":{"timestamp":" 946812285660"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAADA"," userResponse":" MSAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812285818","data":{"timestamp":" 946812285818"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812286583","data":{"timestamp":" 946812286583"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812291568","data":{"timestamp":" 946812291568"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIFUNGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812294676","data":{"timestamp":" 946812294676"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812296951","data":{"timestamp":" 946812296951"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZETU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812298775","data":{"timestamp":" 946812298775"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812300810","data":{"timestamp":" 946812300809"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812303593","data":{"timestamp":" 946812303593"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AJILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812305788","data":{"timestamp":" 946812305787"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812308278","data":{"timestamp":" 946812308278"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812310272","data":{"timestamp":" 946812310271"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIFUNGA"," userResponse":" TULIFUNGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812310758","data":{"timestamp":" 946812310758"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812311288","data":{"timestamp":" 946812311288"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZETU"," userResponse":" ZETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812312073","data":{"timestamp":" 946812312073"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPEMA"," userResponse":" MAPEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812312728","data":{"timestamp":" 946812312728"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812313374","data":{"timestamp":" 946812313374"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AJILI"," userResponse":" AJILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812313457","data":{"timestamp":" 946812313457"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812314076","data":{"timestamp":" 946812314075"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIZI"," userResponse":" WIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812318313","data":{"timestamp":" 946812318313"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812320803","data":{"timestamp":" 946812320803"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812323779","data":{"timestamp":" 946812323778"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812326849","data":{"timestamp":" 946812326849"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIACHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812335503","data":{"timestamp":" 946812335503"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812338180","data":{"timestamp":" 946812338180"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812341840","data":{"timestamp":" 946812341840"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812344872","data":{"timestamp":" 946812344872"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812347687","data":{"timestamp":" 946812347687"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812351363","data":{"timestamp":" 946812351363"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812353791","data":{"timestamp":" 946812353791"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIPA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812355448","data":{"timestamp":" 946812355447"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812357437","data":{"timestamp":" 946812357437"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" BAADHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812357570","data":{"timestamp":" 946812357570"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812358504","data":{"timestamp":" 946812358504"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812359567","data":{"timestamp":" 946812359567"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIACHA"," userResponse":" WALIACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812360220","data":{"timestamp":" 946812360220"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812360664","data":{"timestamp":" 946812360664"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812361290","data":{"timestamp":" 946812361290"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812361824","data":{"timestamp":" 946812361824"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812362298","data":{"timestamp":" 946812362298"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" WAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812363662","data":{"timestamp":" 946812363662"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812364306","data":{"timestamp":" 946812364306"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIPA"," userResponse":" KULIPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812364890","data":{"timestamp":" 946812364890"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARO"," userResponse":" KARO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812370865","data":{"timestamp":" 946812370864"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASICHANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812373576","data":{"timestamp":" 946812373576"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812376710","data":{"timestamp":" 946812376709"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812379981","data":{"timestamp":" 946812379981"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812383027","data":{"timestamp":" 946812383027"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812386461","data":{"timestamp":" 946812386461"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812388964","data":{"timestamp":" 946812388964"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812390879","data":{"timestamp":" 946812390878"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASICHANA"," userResponse":" WASICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812391265","data":{"timestamp":" 946812391265"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADOGO"," userResponse":" WADOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812392262","data":{"timestamp":" 946812392261"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFANYA"," userResponse":" WALIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812392766","data":{"timestamp":" 946812392766"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812393738","data":{"timestamp":" 946812393737"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812394392","data":{"timestamp":" 946812394392"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812395025","data":{"timestamp":" 946812395024"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYA"," userResponse":" YAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812399775","data":{"timestamp":" 946812399775"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812403484","data":{"timestamp":" 946812403484"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812410073","data":{"timestamp":" 946812410073"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIRANDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812412400","data":{"timestamp":" 946812412400"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812415302","data":{"timestamp":" 946812415302"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812416884","data":{"timestamp":" 946812416884"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812419387","data":{"timestamp":" 946812419387"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812422668","data":{"timestamp":" 946812422668"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIFANYIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812424769","data":{"timestamp":" 946812424769"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812426874","data":{"timestamp":" 946812426874"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812429080","data":{"timestamp":" 946812429080"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHAMBANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812430949","data":{"timestamp":" 946812430948"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" WAVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812431712","data":{"timestamp":" 946812431712"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADOGO"," userResponse":" WADOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812432538","data":{"timestamp":" 946812432537"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIRANDA"," userResponse":" WALIRANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812433039","data":{"timestamp":" 946812433039"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANDA"," userResponse":" RANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812433989","data":{"timestamp":" 946812433988"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812434626","data":{"timestamp":" 946812434626"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812435248","data":{"timestamp":" 946812435247"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812436208","data":{"timestamp":" 946812436208"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIFANYIA"," userResponse":" WAKIFANYIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812436667","data":{"timestamp":" 946812436667"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812437146","data":{"timestamp":" 946812437144"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812438122","data":{"timestamp":" 946812438122"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHAMBANI"," userResponse":" MASHAMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812443487","data":{"timestamp":" 946812443487"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812446362","data":{"timestamp":" 946812446361"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIPOVUMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812450466","data":{"timestamp":" 946812450466"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIPEPERUSHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812454274","data":{"timestamp":" 946812454274"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARATASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812456421","data":{"timestamp":" 946812456421"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAFU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812458522","data":{"timestamp":" 946812458522"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812461655","data":{"timestamp":" 946812461655"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUZIANGIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812463903","data":{"timestamp":" 946812463903"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812467153","data":{"timestamp":" 946812467153"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812471491","data":{"timestamp":" 946812471489"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812473366","data":{"timestamp":" 946812473366"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812474676","data":{"timestamp":" 946812474675"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIPOVUMA"," userResponse":" ULIPOVUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812476411","data":{"timestamp":" 946812476411"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIPEPERUSHA"," userResponse":" ULIPEPERUSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812477204","data":{"timestamp":" 946812477204"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARATASI"," userResponse":" KARATASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812478039","data":{"timestamp":" 946812478038"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAFU"," userResponse":" CHAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812478502","data":{"timestamp":" 946812478502"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812479716","data":{"timestamp":" 946812479716"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUZIANGIKA"," userResponse":" KUZIANGIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812480740","data":{"timestamp":" 946812480740"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITINI"," userResponse":" MITINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812481193","data":{"timestamp":" 946812481193"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812481807","data":{"timestamp":" 946812481807"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UANI"," userResponse":" UANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812484502","data":{"timestamp":" 946812484502"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812487129","data":{"timestamp":" 946812487129"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812490073","data":{"timestamp":" 946812490073"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKATWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812492591","data":{"timestamp":" 946812492591"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812497002","data":{"timestamp":" 946812497002"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPANDE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812499750","data":{"timestamp":" 946812499750"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812505858","data":{"timestamp":" 946812505858"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUPA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812509975","data":{"timestamp":" 946812509975"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIVYOTUPWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812511675","data":{"timestamp":" 946812511675"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812513468","data":{"timestamp":" 946812513468"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812515649","data":{"timestamp":" 946812515648"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812516254","data":{"timestamp":" 946812516254"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812517188","data":{"timestamp":" 946812517188"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKATWA"," userResponse":" WALIKATWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812517376","data":{"timestamp":" 946812517376"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812518123","data":{"timestamp":" 946812518123"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPANDE"," userResponse":" VIPANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812518367","data":{"timestamp":" 946812518367"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYA"," userResponse":" VYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812518991","data":{"timestamp":" 946812518991"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUPA"," userResponse":" CHUPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812520374","data":{"timestamp":" 946812520374"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIVYOTUPWA"," userResponse":" VILIVYOTUPWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812520718","data":{"timestamp":" 946812520718"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVYO"," userResponse":" OVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812521191","data":{"timestamp":" 946812521191"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVYO"," userResponse":" OVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812525870","data":{"timestamp":" 946812525869"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812529130","data":{"timestamp":" 946812529129"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812534753","data":{"timestamp":" 946812534753"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812539547","data":{"timestamp":" 946812539547"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFEREJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812549964","data":{"timestamp":" 946812549964"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812552507","data":{"timestamp":" 946812552507"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812554487","data":{"timestamp":" 946812554487"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKAUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812556446","data":{"timestamp":" 946812556445"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812559282","data":{"timestamp":" 946812559282"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITUNGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812561399","data":{"timestamp":" 946812561398"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812565185","data":{"timestamp":" 946812565185"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKAWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812571164","data":{"timestamp":" 946812571164"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUPU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812573055","data":{"timestamp":" 946812573054"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" HALAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812573511","data":{"timestamp":" 946812573507"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812574167","data":{"timestamp":" 946812574166"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812575467","data":{"timestamp":" 946812575467"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFEREJI"," userResponse":" MFEREJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812575660","data":{"timestamp":" 946812575660"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812576275","data":{"timestamp":" 946812576274"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812577519","data":{"timestamp":" 946812577519"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKAUKA"," userResponse":" ULIKAUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812578203","data":{"timestamp":" 946812578203"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812579046","data":{"timestamp":" 946812579046"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITUNGI"," userResponse":" MITUNGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812579469","data":{"timestamp":" 946812579469"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" YETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812580620","data":{"timestamp":" 946812580620"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKAWA"," userResponse":" IKAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812581341","data":{"timestamp":" 946812581341"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUPU"," userResponse":" TUPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812584547","data":{"timestamp":" 946812584547"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812587913","data":{"timestamp":" 946812587913"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITEMBEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812590643","data":{"timestamp":" 946812590643"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812593351","data":{"timestamp":" 946812593351"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812596062","data":{"timestamp":" 946812596062"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812597894","data":{"timestamp":" 946812597893"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812604263","data":{"timestamp":" 946812604263"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWAALIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812607666","data":{"timestamp":" 946812607665"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812610172","data":{"timestamp":" 946812610172"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHUDHURIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812612865","data":{"timestamp":" 946812612865"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUTANO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812616182","data":{"timestamp":" 946812616182"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812622907","data":{"timestamp":" 946812622907"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJIJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812624973","data":{"timestamp":" 946812624972"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABANGU"," userResponse":" BABANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812626235","data":{"timestamp":" 946812626234"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITEMBEA"," userResponse":" ALITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812627018","data":{"timestamp":" 946812627017"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812627644","data":{"timestamp":" 946812627644"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812628418","data":{"timestamp":" 946812628418"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812628973","data":{"timestamp":" 946812628973"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812630276","data":{"timestamp":" 946812630276"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWAALIKA"," userResponse":" AKIWAALIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812630792","data":{"timestamp":" 946812630792"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812632026","data":{"timestamp":" 946812632026"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHUDHURIA"," userResponse":" KUHUDHURIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812632850","data":{"timestamp":" 946812632850"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUTANO"," userResponse":" MKUTANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812633066","data":{"timestamp":" 946812633065"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812633908","data":{"timestamp":" 946812633907"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJIJI"," userResponse":" KUJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812640925","data":{"timestamp":" 946812640925"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812643565","data":{"timestamp":" 946812643564"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUSANYIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812645747","data":{"timestamp":" 946812645746"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812648697","data":{"timestamp":" 946812648697"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812651275","data":{"timestamp":" 946812651274"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812655133","data":{"timestamp":" 946812655133"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812657681","data":{"timestamp":" 946812657680"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812662391","data":{"timestamp":" 946812662391"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812665004","data":{"timestamp":" 946812665001"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIPOKEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812667244","data":{"timestamp":" 946812667243"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812669395","data":{"timestamp":" 946812669395"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812672867","data":{"timestamp":" 946812672867"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAADA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812674611","data":{"timestamp":" 946812674611"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812675873","data":{"timestamp":" 946812675873"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUSANYIKA"," userResponse":" WALIKUSANYIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812676455","data":{"timestamp":" 946812676454"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812676537","data":{"timestamp":" 946812676537"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812676961","data":{"timestamp":" 946812676961"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812677515","data":{"timestamp":" 946812677515"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULE"," userResponse":" ULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812677910","data":{"timestamp":" 946812677910"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULE"," userResponse":" ULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812678834","data":{"timestamp":" 946812678833"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAKO"," userResponse":" AMBAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812679688","data":{"timestamp":" 946812679688"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIPOKEA"," userResponse":" TULIPOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812680252","data":{"timestamp":" 946812680252"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812680496","data":{"timestamp":" 946812680495"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812681250","data":{"timestamp":" 946812681250"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAADA"," userResponse":" MSAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812685772","data":{"timestamp":" 946812685772"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812690839","data":{"timestamp":" 946812690839"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIMAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812692669","data":{"timestamp":" 946812692669"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812695465","data":{"timestamp":" 946812695465"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812697434","data":{"timestamp":" 946812697434"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKUNDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812701586","data":{"timestamp":" 946812701586"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812704183","data":{"timestamp":" 946812704183"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812707074","data":{"timestamp":" 946812707074"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812712511","data":{"timestamp":" 946812712510"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUREKEBISHE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812715375","data":{"timestamp":" 946812715374"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812725931","data":{"timestamp":" 946812725930"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHETU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812727768","data":{"timestamp":" 946812727768"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABANGU"," userResponse":" BABANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812728650","data":{"timestamp":" 946812728650"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIMAMA"," userResponse":" ALISIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812729764","data":{"timestamp":" 946812729764"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812730238","data":{"timestamp":" 946812730238"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812731102","data":{"timestamp":" 946812731102"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKUNDI"," userResponse":" KIKUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812731496","data":{"timestamp":" 946812731496"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812732229","data":{"timestamp":" 946812732229"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" KUSEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812733533","data":{"timestamp":" 946812733533"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" LAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812734737","data":{"timestamp":" 946812734737"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUREKEBISHE"," userResponse":" TUREKEBISHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812735283","data":{"timestamp":" 946812735282"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812735917","data":{"timestamp":" 946812735917"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHETU"," userResponse":" CHETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812739874","data":{"timestamp":" 946812739873"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812742482","data":{"timestamp":" 946812742482"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812746118","data":{"timestamp":" 946812746117"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEPANDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812748917","data":{"timestamp":" 946812748917"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812751627","data":{"timestamp":" 946812751627"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812753783","data":{"timestamp":" 946812753783"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812757349","data":{"timestamp":" 946812757349"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812762620","data":{"timestamp":" 946812762620"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812765727","data":{"timestamp":" 946812765726"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812768830","data":{"timestamp":" 946812768830"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UWANJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812771703","data":{"timestamp":" 946812771703"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812774662","data":{"timestamp":" 946812774662"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812778545","data":{"timestamp":" 946812778545"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812780753","data":{"timestamp":" 946812780753"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUMA"," userResponse":" JUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812781955","data":{"timestamp":" 946812781955"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIYEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812782809","data":{"timestamp":" 946812782809"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEPANDA"," userResponse":" AMEPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812783411","data":{"timestamp":" 946812783411"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812784350","data":{"timestamp":" 946812784350"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812784634","data":{"timestamp":" 946812784634"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812785312","data":{"timestamp":" 946812785311"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812786337","data":{"timestamp":" 946812786337"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWEZA"," userResponse":" NAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812787421","data":{"timestamp":" 946812787421"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFISHA"," userResponse":" KUSAFISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812788054","data":{"timestamp":" 946812788054"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UWANJA"," userResponse":" UWANJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812788208","data":{"timestamp":" 946812788208"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812788612","data":{"timestamp":" 946812788612"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812789317","data":{"timestamp":" 946812789317"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" YETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812796634","data":{"timestamp":" 946812796634"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812799893","data":{"timestamp":" 946812799892"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812801955","data":{"timestamp":" 946812801955"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812804174","data":{"timestamp":" 946812804174"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKAMO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812808203","data":{"timestamp":" 946812808203"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812810425","data":{"timestamp":" 946812810425"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812814244","data":{"timestamp":" 946812814244"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812817082","data":{"timestamp":" 946812817082"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAWEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812820770","data":{"timestamp":" 946812820769"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUNGANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812823637","data":{"timestamp":" 946812823636"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812825652","data":{"timestamp":" 946812825652"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPANDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812827740","data":{"timestamp":" 946812827740"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812829721","data":{"timestamp":" 946812829721"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812830298","data":{"timestamp":" 946812830298"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812830481","data":{"timestamp":" 946812830481"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812831257","data":{"timestamp":" 946812831257"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKAMO"," userResponse":" MAKAMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812832084","data":{"timestamp":" 946812832081"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812833064","data":{"timestamp":" 946812833063"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" SISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812834031","data":{"timestamp":" 946812834031"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" WANAWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812835037","data":{"timestamp":" 946812835035"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAWEZA"," userResponse":" TUNAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812835795","data":{"timestamp":" 946812835795"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUNGANA"," userResponse":" KUUNGANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812835987","data":{"timestamp":" 946812835987"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812836610","data":{"timestamp":" 946812836609"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPANDA"," userResponse":" KUPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812837417","data":{"timestamp":" 946812837416"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812966890","data":{"timestamp":" 946812966889"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMME"," userResponse":" KUSEMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812972685","data":{"timestamp":" 946812972685"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMME"," userResponse":" START_MWANAMME"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812974188","data":{"timestamp":" 946812974188"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMME"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946812977552","data":{"timestamp":" 946812977552"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813001274","data":{"timestamp":" 946813001274"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIMAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813008749","data":{"timestamp":" 946813008749"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813014103","data":{"timestamp":" 946813014103"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813016046","data":{"timestamp":" 946813016046"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAUME"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813024473","data":{"timestamp":" 946813024473"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATACHIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813033399","data":{"timestamp":" 946813033399"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813034970","data":{"timestamp":" 946813034970"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813037424","data":{"timestamp":" 946813037424"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813039432","data":{"timestamp":" 946813039432"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMME"," userResponse":" MWANAMME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813040276","data":{"timestamp":" 946813040275"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813041228","data":{"timestamp":" 946813041228"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIMAMA"," userResponse":" ALISIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813041422","data":{"timestamp":" 946813041422"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813042066","data":{"timestamp":" 946813042066"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" KUSEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813043240","data":{"timestamp":" 946813043240"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAUME"," userResponse":" WANAUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813044133","data":{"timestamp":" 946813044133"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATACHIMBA"," userResponse":" WATACHIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813044696","data":{"timestamp":" 946813044696"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISIMA"," userResponse":" KISIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813044949","data":{"timestamp":" 946813044949"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813045632","data":{"timestamp":" 946813045632"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813050954","data":{"timestamp":" 946813050953"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOTE"," userResponse":" SOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813053877","data":{"timestamp":" 946813053877"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813056406","data":{"timestamp":" 946813056406"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813059494","data":{"timestamp":" 946813059494"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813062881","data":{"timestamp":" 946813062881"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813069328","data":{"timestamp":" 946813069327"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813074389","data":{"timestamp":" 946813074388"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUBADILISHE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813076749","data":{"timestamp":" 946813076749"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813081717","data":{"timestamp":" 946813081717"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813083767","data":{"timestamp":" 946813083766"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOTE"," userResponse":" SOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813084641","data":{"timestamp":" 946813084641"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULISEMA"," userResponse":" TULISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813084878","data":{"timestamp":" 946813084878"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813085549","data":{"timestamp":" 946813085549"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813086032","data":{"timestamp":" 946813086032"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813087416","data":{"timestamp":" 946813087415"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" LAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813088539","data":{"timestamp":" 946813088539"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUBADILISHE"," userResponse":" TUBADILISHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813089275","data":{"timestamp":" 946813089273"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAISHA"," userResponse":" MAISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813089996","data":{"timestamp":" 946813089996"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" YETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813094334","data":{"timestamp":" 946813094333"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813095979","data":{"timestamp":" 946813095979"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813098127","data":{"timestamp":" 946813098127"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813098446","data":{"timestamp":" 946813098445"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813098599","data":{"timestamp":" 946813098599"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..22.off2.17__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813169362","data":{"timestamp":" 946813169362"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 737337a5-8ca8-41ca-a8ec-b0b8dcf08ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813180574","data":{"timestamp":" 946813180573"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 3ef5a571-91c0-40ba-8f39-849b2ff792b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813181269","data":{"timestamp":" 946813181269"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 3ef5a571-91c0-40ba-8f39-849b2ff792b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813182224","data":{"timestamp":" 946813182224"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 3ef5a571-91c0-40ba-8f39-849b2ff792b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813182421","data":{"timestamp":" 946813182421"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 3ef5a571-91c0-40ba-8f39-849b2ff792b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813183015","data":{"timestamp":" 946813183015"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 3ef5a571-91c0-40ba-8f39-849b2ff792b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWITU"," userResponse":" MWITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813183021","data":{"timestamp":" 946813183020"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 3ef5a571-91c0-40ba-8f39-849b2ff792b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946813183112","data":{"timestamp":" 946813183112"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 3ef5a571-91c0-40ba-8f39-849b2ff792b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWITU"," userResponse":" MWITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819387037","data":{"timestamp":" 946819387036"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 3ef5a571-91c0-40ba-8f39-849b2ff792b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819393865","data":{"timestamp":" 946819393865"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_142017"," gameId":" 3ef5a571-91c0-40ba-8f39-849b2ff792b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}